Enzo Vezzaro

UI / UX designer and Web developer



enzovezzaro05@gmail.com



+39 389 489 9604





Pavia, Italy Open to move



enzovezzaro.com insuladigitalstudio.com





github.com/EnzoVezzaro



Hello, I'm Enzo. I love being creative, exploring and broadening my horizons, create high quality product and giving stunning user experience to my products. I'm an enthusiast of user interface, experience design, and clean and usable coding.

Experiences

May 2017 - Present

Front-End Developer, UI Designer Eleva.it

Pavia, Italy

January 2016 - Present

Head Developer / Art Director Vapecloudshop.com

Santo Domingo, RD

August 2015 - January 2016

Head Developer Thevapelifestore.com

Hollywood, CA

September 2014 - Present

CEO

InsulaDigitalStudio.com

Creating Web/Native Expiriences with modern web technoligies.

Education

2017 - 2018

Google Developer Challenge Scholarship: Mobile Web

Worldwide

2012 -

Computer Science Degree (in process)

Los Angeles City College

Los Angeles, California

2006 - 2010

Multimedia and Communication Diploma

I.P.S. Americo D'Aschio

Vicenza, Italy

Languages

Spanish: Native Italian: Native

Tools

Mac OS X Atom Sketch Adobe Suite Affinity Suite Slack Trello InVision Git

Design Skills

Photography Prototype design Web design Responsive design App Design



Development Skills

SASS, JADE, Gulp, Foundation, Bootstrap Javascript, ¡Query, Firebase, Netlify, Moltin, Git, CLI, AWS, React (Native). Loading . . .

Hobies













